[{"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113395fa", "question": "What were the names of rival gangs in \"West Side Story\"?", "answer": "The Jets and The Sharks", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c778", "question": "What animal species were depicted as evil characters in \"The Wonderful Wizard of Oz\"?", "answer": "Monkeys", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113399fc", "question": "What 1992 film features the characters Colonel Nathan Jessup and Lieutenant Daniel Kaffee?", "answer": "A Few Good Men", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af50", "question": "What happened on September 1, 1939 that led to Britain and France declaring war on Germany?", "answer": "Invasion of Poland", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b8b5", "question": "A quincentenary celebrates how many years?", "answer": "500", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b408", "question": "What year was margarine first patented?", "answer": "1869", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58ab15b4baab681b0929217c", "question": "In what year did the BBC debut the \u201cTop Gear\u201d TV series?", "answer": "1977", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388e2", "question": "What year was the first book of the \"Bourne Trilogy\" series first published?", "answer": "1980", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a065", "question": "According to the song what did my true love give to me on the fifth day of Christmas?", "answer": "Five gold rings", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a59e", "question": "In what mountains is Camp David?", "answer": "Appalachian Mountains", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "601b4ae449076251badbeabd", "question": "Who earned the nickname \"Moses\" in the Underground Railroad?", "answer": "Harriet Tubman -- One of the most well-known coordinators of the Underground Railroad, she helped more than 70 slaves to freedom.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b01c", "question": "What U.S. President declared \"The ballot is stronger than the bullet\"?", "answer": "Abraham Lincoln", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c59", "question": "Who played the role of the bodyguard in the 1992 movie \"The Bodyguard\"?", "answer": "Kevin Costner", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff2148831a458464a93c458", "question": "A sentence, verse, etc., that includes all the letters of the alphabet is called what?", "answer": "Pangram", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f2a", "question": "Who wrote \"The Pisan Cantos\" while in prison?", "answer": "Ezra Pound", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a5d9", "question": "What does the brass plate on Number 10 Downing Street say?", "answer": "First Lord of the Admiralty", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b06e", "question": "What was the infamous pseudonym of William Bonney?", "answer": "Billy the Kid", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fdfb819003d27d341092bba", "question": "What is the capital of Morocco?", "answer": "Rabat", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133abd4", "question": "Which state is the Hoover Dam located in?", "answer": "It lies on the border between Arizona and Nevada", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c5b3", "question": "How many calories are stored in 1 pound of body fat?", "answer": "3500", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe655d1ae7e414034b5aebb", "question": "A golden apple sparked which famous war?", "answer": "The Trojan War", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5901dcfd709c1c34536e6eb7", "question": "On Saturday Night Live, who played the recurring character known as \"Samurai Futaba\"?", "answer": "John Belushi", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b783", "question": "Cyanide is often said to have the bitter aroma of what?", "answer": "Almonds", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fed2c08ec223966ae8f8915", "question": "What Vin Diesel film did David Twohy direct?", "answer": "\"The Chronicles Of Riddick\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c3ba", "question": "Which is the fourth planet from the Sun?", "answer": "Mars", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339574", "question": "In, Santa Baby by Madonna what kind of fur does she want him to slip under the tree?", "answer": "A sable", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bdf4", "question": "What was the nickname of restaurateur Dave Thomas' second daughter?", "answer": "Wendy", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ded", "question": "What TV show's theme song was called \"The Fishin' Hole\"?", "answer": "The Andy Griffith Show", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe7700beec85e375820b2f3", "question": "What is the smallest national park in Canada?", "answer": "Georgian Bay Islands National Park, Ontario", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339bd1", "question": "Which ABBA song won the 1974 Eurovision Song Contest?", "answer": "Waterloo", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339581", "question": "Which actress-turned-diplomat won a special Oscar for \"outstanding contribution to screen entertainment\" in 1934?", "answer": "Shirley Temple", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113398b3", "question": "What album earned Paul Simon a Grammy Award in 1987?", "answer": "Graceland", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a024", "question": "What is the name of the arrogant male co-anchor of Channel 5 News in the TV show \"Family Guy\"?", "answer": "Tom Tucker", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59f9bbc5364247bf200fb8a7", "question": "Lusaka is the capital of which country?", "answer": "Zambia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5e8a88fa404ad935a7e1a63e", "question": "Which composer began to lose his hearing at age 26?", "answer": "Ludwig van Beethoven", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5921fcf3a4edfd43a087adc6", "question": "What number is represented by \"D\" in Roman numerals?", "answer": "500", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b24", "question": "In the Beach Boys song \"California Girls\", which girls are 'hip'?", "answer": "East coast girls", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "600781e8bd51d85e222ab650", "question": "Which of Picasso's paintings was considered immoral when it was first exhibited in 1916?", "answer": "Les Demoiselles d'Avignon\u00a0(The Young Ladies of Avignon), a depiction of 5 Barcelona prostitutes, was deemed immoral by the public.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fea3856ff048f679a45ab23", "question": "Who is considered the \"father\" of organic chemistry?", "answer": "Friedrich W\u00f6hler", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fcc1c1ec97eb73f6a51a272", "question": "Including underwater mountains, what is the longest mountain range on Earth?", "answer": "Ocean Ridge", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c4ad", "question": "What is usually added to tin to make solder?", "answer": "Lead", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5ffb69685dad637d903c8847", "question": "Who played the wife of Goose in the film \"Top Gun\"?", "answer": "Meg Ryan", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133963b", "question": "Which Disney's cartoon character's love interest is named Faline?", "answer": "Bambi's", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a6aa", "question": "What cave, found in central Kentucky, is the world's longest cave system?", "answer": "Mammoth Cave", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59ca3e4a44f0f6af5b066649", "question": "In mathematics, which prefix refers to 10 to the power of 24?", "answer": "Yotta", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a784", "question": "How many US state capital city\u2019s names begin with the letter \"S\"?", "answer": "6", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113399cc", "question": "Who played Inspector Clouseau in the 1964 movie \"The Pink Panther\"?", "answer": "Peter Sellers", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c38d", "question": "What is gymnophobia the fear of?", "answer": "Nudity", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b416", "question": "What year did Sierra Leone gain its independence from the UK?", "answer": "1961", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c512", "question": "What is the largest muscle in the human body?", "answer": "Gluteus maximus", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe5265c1bf59ab7d2e380f6", "question": "What is the coldest permanently inhabited town on Earth?", "answer": "Oymyakon, Russia", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59412802bab1e6f9796f1b59", "question": "In which card game might you be dealt a \"Yarborough\" hand?", "answer": "Bridge", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0dc", "question": "\"Little Bastard\" was the nickname given to the Porsche 550 Spyder that killed what acting icon in a crash?", "answer": "James Dean", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58c89d85011619dd6d415486", "question": "What country\u2019s Royal Wedding was Ike obsessed with in Season 15 of South Park?", "answer": "Canada", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e6a", "question": "Who played the blind character in the movie \"Ray\"?", "answer": "Jamie Foxx", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59d184923b17032616b590fa", "question": "The fisrt armed daylight bank robbery in the US is said to have occured in what year?", "answer": "1866", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a186", "question": "In the cartoon \"Wacky Races\", who drove the Crimson Haybaler?", "answer": "The Red Max", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a44c", "question": "In what country was the Terracotta Army sealed underground?", "answer": "China", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fdfbf4b003d27d341092bd4", "question": "Which country holds the record for both the coldest and hottest temperatures in South America?", "answer": "Argentina", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ddc", "question": "From what language did English borrow the word \"dungarees\"?", "answer": "Hindi", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b70", "question": "What city did the S.S. Minnow leave from on its three-hour tour on the original TV series \"Gilligan's Island\"?", "answer": "Honolulu", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fecc1d7ec223966ae8f886e", "question": "The \"Tina\" in Tina Fey is short for what name?", "answer": "Stamatina", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5b7abb326490a8cc1a6e5295", "question": "In computer programming, which logic gate outputs TRUE if both inputs are TRUE?", "answer": "AND", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59cdb50365ff7d326b622a8c", "question": "Which play is believed to be Shakespeare's first tragedy?", "answer": "Titus Andronicus", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a08f", "question": "Who recorded the albums \"Cuts Both Ways\", and \"Into The Light\"?", "answer": "Gloria Estefan", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a635", "question": "The Silicon Valley is located in what California valley?", "answer": "Santa Clara Valley", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d15", "question": "What comic strip features a family dog named Barfy?", "answer": "The Family Circus", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe6a79620565ad31a57c7eb", "question": "Which state's flag was designed by a 7th grader?", "answer": "Alaska", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a378", "question": "What is the capital of Finland?", "answer": "Helsinki", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5f3", "question": "Which celebrity popularized the \"wedge\" haircut?", "answer": "Dorothy Hamill", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b742", "question": "Who was also known as \"Black Dahlia\"?", "answer": "Elizabeth Short", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e4b", "question": "Who is the Roman equivalent of Dionysus, the Greek god of wine?", "answer": "Bacchus", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339321", "question": "In the movie \"Hangover\", what name did Alan use to refer to his circle of friends?", "answer": "The wolf pack", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c356", "question": "What is odontophobia the fear of?", "answer": "Dentistry", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fea4638ff048f679a45aba0", "question": "The Planting Moon is found in which month?", "answer": "May", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bcf1", "question": "Who's responsible for \"The Ballad of A Thin Man\"?", "answer": "Bob Dylan", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c58f", "question": "During which time period did the stegosaurus walk the earth?", "answer": "Late Jurassic", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fde4a70c6c6b019850c9a75", "question": "Queen Alexandra's father and brother were kings of what country?", "answer": "Denmark", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c577", "question": "What is the chemical symbol for the element \"Cesium\"?", "answer": "Cs", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5ffa40e0c73aa70ea0b70b0b", "question": "Which U.S. state claims to be the diner capital of the world?", "answer": "New Jersey", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5921fd86a4edfd43a087adca", "question": "What can be styled in a \"Half-Windsor\" or a \"Hanover\"?", "answer": "A tie", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd85", "question": "What type of animal is the Japanese monster, Kamacuras?", "answer": "Praying mantis", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe52fb81bf59ab7d2e38117", "question": "Where is Bank of America headquartered?", "answer": "Charlotte, North Carolina", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b70f", "question": "In The Twelve Days of Christmas what did my true love send to me on the third day?", "answer": "Three French Hens", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b3d7", "question": "Who tore up a picture of the Pope on US television in 1992?", "answer": "Sinead O'Connor", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe7761feec85e375820b317", "question": "Where is the Valley of the Moon?", "answer": "Jordan", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a8ea", "question": "In what bay would you find the Andaman and Nicobar islands?", "answer": "The Bay of Bengal", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ff7c3462b316f4693fb67a7", "question": "Monterey Jack is a type of what?", "answer": "Cheese", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5bfdfeacb668d7dfe168b5b0", "question": "The term \"lupine\" refers to which animal?", "answer": "Wolf", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c474", "question": "A tetrahedron is composed of how many triangles?", "answer": "Four", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a3dc", "question": "What became the second independent country in the Americas after the United States?", "answer": "Haiti", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fd2cf3e2596a59cbdfbd36d", "question": "Who said, \"There is only one good, knowledge, and one evil, ignorance\"?", "answer": "Socrates", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c925", "question": "What is a characteristic of a \"nimbus\" cloud?", "answer": "Rain", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5ad7e6f7b24f84e0b9f9ffb5", "question": "Who played Judge Dredd in the 1995 film by the same name?", "answer": "Sylvester Stallone", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a27e", "question": "In which 1989 film did Kevin Costner play the role of Ray Kinsella?", "answer": "Field of Dreams", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ae7", "question": "What city was the setting for the film \"Die Hard\"?", "answer": "Los Angeles", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5febd43a7e83c707845b215a", "question": "What famous actor turned down the role of Trinity in film \"The Matrix\"?", "answer": "Sandra Bullock turned down the role because she had the understanding that Will Smith was in the film.", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5aab2ef258d116dab4aecb44", "question": "What is dendrochronology?", "answer": "Tree ring dating", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5b32354fbf195a31e15d73ad", "question": "Which American comedian was born Benjamin Kubelsky?", "answer": "Jack Benny", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339839", "question": "Who won a Grammy Award for his album \"52nd Street\"?", "answer": "Billy Joel", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fdc1375469bb8041d07a07f", "question": "What did the \"lemon campaign\" advertise in the 60's?", "answer": "Volkswagen", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b40a", "question": "What country gave birth to margarine in 1869?", "answer": "France", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133944a", "question": "Who played the role of Shoeless Joe Jackson in the 1989 movie \"Field of Dreams\"?", "answer": "Ray Liotta", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133943a", "question": "Who played Goose's wife in the 1986 movie \"Top Gun\"?", "answer": "Meg Ryan", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a71", "question": "What is the name of the girl Bruce Springsteen is singing to in the song \"Born to Run\"?", "answer": "Wendy", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338de6", "question": "From what language did English borrow the word \"orangutan\"?", "answer": "Malay", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "6012186963c99d48cd169af2", "question": "Minnesota, it is illegal to tease what type of animal?", "answer": "Skunk", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58d115314fea7fe947a22264", "question": "Who produced the Beatles' \"Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band\" album?", "answer": "George Martin", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5b358dba5db0d66a186cb563", "question": "If a chemical is \"anhydrous\", what does it not contain?", "answer": "Water", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a255", "question": "What country was Alfred Hitchcock born?", "answer": "England", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113394d7", "question": "What made-for-TV movie starred Alfre Woodard as Eunice Evers?", "answer": "Miss Evers' Boys", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fef96c16ce05a3942286ea0", "question": "What kind of sneakers did Rocky wear in his training montage?", "answer": "Chuck Taylor", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b8dd", "question": "What was Jesse Ventura's wrestling nickname?", "answer": "Jesse \"The Body\" Ventura", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fec8de5ec223966ae8f8859", "question": "What character does Will Ferrell play in the movie \"Anchorman\"?", "answer": "Ron Burgundy", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e41", "question": "What 1964 Broadway hit centered on a milkman and his five daughters?", "answer": "Fiddler on the Roof", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113399ce", "question": "In what 2006 film does a family travel in a VW microbus to get to a beauty pageant?", "answer": "Little Miss Sunshine", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9af", "question": "What mountain is the tallest point in Ecuador?", "answer": "Chimborazo", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fb0882bcf631c2414a13b5a", "question": "What does \"Valar Morghulis\" mean in High Valyrian?", "answer": "All men must die", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58b8cd1794b094db915830a4", "question": "How many Academy Award nominations did Leonardo DiCaprio receive before finally winning the award for Best Actor in 2016?", "answer": "6", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5900887ecf842fa4c4ba9689", "question": "Who wrote the novel \"Across the River and into the Trees\"?", "answer": "Ernest Hemmingway", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "60173fb844491cbd7c5a17b5", "question": "What was created by the people who produced the academic journal called the\u00a0\"Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists\" in 1947?", "answer": "The Doomsday Clock -- It was created after humanity entered the Nuclear Age after the dropping of atomic bombs on Japan in 1945.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f7b", "question": "What was George Thorogood's backing band?", "answer": "The Destroyers", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e4c", "question": "What athlete had a part in the movie \"Blazing Saddles\"?", "answer": "Alex Karras", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd09", "question": "What was the original brand of cereal pitched by Tony the Tiger?", "answer": "Kellogg's Sugar Frosted Flakes", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5be57c9c5415ba52ed6f0aa3", "question": "What is Sterling Archer's codename on the cartoon series \"Archer\"?", "answer": "Duchess", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6015de71fe83fe1f2a824b6a", "question": "What percent of the casualties in World War II were civilians?", "answer": "60%", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391a6", "question": "What movie starred Mel Gibson as William Wallace?", "answer": "Braveheart", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133caa4", "question": "With what is sulfur and charcoal mixed to make gunpowder?", "answer": "Saltpeter", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa3f", "question": "What is the capital of China?", "answer": "Beijing", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "591c374c815febcc896f926f", "question": "Who wrote the detective novel \"The Maltese Falcon\"?", "answer": "Dashiell Hammett", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f45", "question": "Who created the character of Paddington?", "answer": "Michael Bond", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5febbaef7e83c707845b2147", "question": "Which character in the \"Street Fighter\" series was inspired by martial-arts legend Bruce Lee?", "answer": "Fei Long", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b093", "question": "What large amphitheater in Rome was opened to showcase gladiator combat?", "answer": "The Colosseum", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fef5a2a6ce05a3942286e0a", "question": "Who was the first player in NBA history to play in over 1,000 consecutive games?", "answer": "A. C. Green", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa58", "question": "Which is the largest of the Canary Islands?", "answer": "Tenerife", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5a25f14f6682715b82711cde", "question": "What year was the ice cream cone patented in the US?", "answer": "1903", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d2f", "question": "Which two actresses on TV's \"Charlie's Angels\" were meant to be portraying sisters?", "answer": "Farrah Fawcett-Majors and Cheryl Ladd", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ad7ea81b24f84e0b9f9ffd5", "question": "Homichlophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Fog or humidity", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7f5", "question": "What Australian island is named for the man who circumnavigated Australia and discovered New Zealand?", "answer": "Tasmania", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b03d", "question": "In 1969, what woman said \"No woman, in my time, will ever be Prime Minister\"?", "answer": "Margaret Thatcher", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe6a96e20565ad31a57c803", "question": "Where did President Franklin D. Roosevelt die?", "answer": "Warm Springs, Georgia", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a90e", "question": "What major river runs through Dublin?", "answer": "Liffey", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a41f", "question": "What is the modern day equivalent of Asia Minor?", "answer": "Turkey", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5febb9a07e83c707845b213c", "question": "What common sensation has the scientific name \"sphenopalatine ganglioneuralgia\"?", "answer": "Brain freeze", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bfab", "question": "What are Tracy Thorn and Ben Watt collectively known as?", "answer": "Everything But The Girl", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fecd2a0ec223966ae8f88c5", "question": "In \"The Wolf of Wall Street\", what did the actors snort in scenes that involved cocaine?", "answer": "Vitamin B", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5f5", "question": "Ham is taken from what part of a pig?", "answer": "The hind leg", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f7e", "question": "Who killed Macbeth?", "answer": "Macduff", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133949d", "question": "What actor played the role of Captain James T. Kirk in the original Star Trek series?", "answer": "William Shatner", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339604", "question": "What nickname does Marshall Samuel Gerard go by in the 1993 movie \"The Fugitive\"?", "answer": "Big Dog", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b80f", "question": "What two snacks are mentioned in \"Take Me Out to the Ballgame\"?", "answer": "Peanuts and Cracker Jack", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59049f03cf93664eb10486b7", "question": "What US state is home to the \"One Shell Square\" skyscraper?", "answer": "Louisiana", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b6d3", "question": "What event in a decathlon takes the athletes to the greatest height?", "answer": "Pole vault", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a6ee", "question": "Which US state is nicknamed the \"Golden State\"?", "answer": "California", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5bfdfffcb668d7dfe168b5be", "question": "Who declined a Pulitzer Prize for his book \"Arrowsmith\"?", "answer": "Sinclair Lewis", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a16", "question": "What was the name of the guy Sam has a crush on in the movie \"Sixteen Candles\"?", "answer": "Jake Ryan", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58be2d788faf425cf37add7e", "question": "The game \"Cities: Skylines\" was developed by which Finnish video game company?", "answer": "Colossal Order", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a0ca", "question": "Who sang the song \"Foolish Games\"?", "answer": "Jewel", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5904a4f5cf93664eb10486c7", "question": "What are the nicknames of the twin sisters who work as enforcers for Darcy Parker, in the \"Strangers in Paradise\" comic series?", "answer": "Tambi and Bambi", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b22a", "question": "Whittaker Chambers hid Alger Hiss' purloined State Department documents in a hollowed-out what?", "answer": "Pumpkin", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c276", "question": "What is September's birthstone?", "answer": "Sapphire", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113392b2", "question": "Which actress, famous for her fruit hats, was the inspiration for the Chiquita banana logo?", "answer": "Carmen Miranda", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b91", "question": "What daily comic strip features occasional visits from Bob the Dinosaur, \"king of the wedgies\"?", "answer": "Dilbert", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396d6", "question": "Tommy Lee Jones and Al Gore were roommates at what university?", "answer": "Harvard", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c23b", "question": "Which European city is served by Galileo Galilei Airport?", "answer": "Pisa", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58ab14fabaab681b09292179", "question": "Which Formula One world champion assisted Honda in the final design stages of the NSX?", "answer": "Ayrton Senna", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd81f49d0de9af39e9d4695", "question": "How long did China's one-child policy last?", "answer": "35 years", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113392e0", "question": "Which Captain & Tennille hit was written by Neil Sedaka?", "answer": "Love Will Keep Us Together", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe69cff20565ad31a57c772", "question": "Who was the first Boy Scout to be elected president of the United States?", "answer": "John F. Kennedy", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be6f", "question": "What is the Minute Maid Park also known as?", "answer": "The Juice Box", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5febaa3e7e83c707845b20dd", "question": "How many main layers make up the earth's atmosphere?", "answer": "5", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a32a", "question": "Which character did Nick Nolte play in the 1982 film \"48 Hrs.\"?", "answer": "Jack Cates", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b3a", "question": "In the John Cougar song \"Jack & Diane\", what are they eating outside the Tastee-Freez?", "answer": "A chili dog", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ec6", "question": "What's the subject of the 1969 memoir \"Thirteen Days\"?", "answer": "The Cuban Missile Crisis", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ff7c26d2b316f4693fb67a0", "question": "How many steps does the Empire State Building have?", "answer": "1,860", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a5f0", "question": "Into which sea does the Volga river flow?", "answer": "The Caspian Sea", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c59", "question": "Who was the faithful wife of Ulysses in Homer\u2019s \"Odyssey\"?", "answer": "Penelope", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "58be2dac8faf425cf37add81", "question": "What is the capital of the Isle of Man?", "answer": "Douglas", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6018bbedd96d05b23b281651", "question": "The Peloponnesian War was fought between Athens and which other ancient Greek state?", "answer": "Sparta", "category": "history"}, {"id": "600242584be4723ccac22184", "question": "Author Daniel Handler is best known for his children\u2019s books published under which pseudonym?", "answer": "Lemony Snicket", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b691", "question": "In the US, the horn of plenty is a common symbol of which holiday?", "answer": "Thanksgiving", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58f16aa7f7c52aae91cc07df", "question": "In which city is the \"Wailing Wall\"?", "answer": "Jerusalem", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ad7e97db24f84e0b9f9ffce", "question": "What precious metal did alchemists call \"luna\"?", "answer": "Silver", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5cb70e99f96e155acab35d3a", "question": "Who painted \"The Starry Night\"?", "answer": "Vincent van Gogh", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b8f7", "question": "Approximately how many acres is a baseball field?", "answer": "2", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338cfa", "question": "What was the name of King Arthur's sword?", "answer": "Excalibur", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339cd5", "question": "What is the surname of Sesame Street's The Count?", "answer": "Von Count", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe93a6f6bd93ce3a4e5f697", "question": "Who is \"the Science Guy\"?", "answer": "Bill Nye", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5cb70d7bf96e155acab35d33", "question": "What country hosted the first modern Olympic games in 1896?", "answer": "Greece", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59067df9ff9c0647b50a8076", "question": "What is the more common name for the Bigelow Expandable Activity Module that was added to the International Space Station in 2016?", "answer": "BEAM", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a5ea", "question": "Which is the highest waterfall?", "answer": "Angel Falls", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113390f7", "question": "What is the first name of writer H. G. Wells?", "answer": "Herbert", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc7f", "question": "To counter slipping sales, what was marketed, beginning in 1987, as \"the other white meat\"?", "answer": "Pork", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b9f9", "question": "In what state did former Illinois Governor Rod Blagojavich begin serving his 14 year sentence for corruption?", "answer": "Colorado", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca06", "question": "What is the Shaddock a variety of?", "answer": "Citrus", "category": "science"}, {"id": "59c1ceb97bd84c0ea43ad43b", "question": "Who is Thomas John Woodward better known as?", "answer": "Tom Jones", "category": "general"}, {"id": "593c4ae6b8198b9a2b07795f", "question": "Which award-winning actress starred in the film \"Shakespeare in Love\"?", "answer": "Gwyneth Paltrow", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c9de", "question": "If you were travelling at Mach II how fast would you be moving?", "answer": "Twice the speed of sound\u00a0", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5952427f736d4be723796b64", "question": "How old was Ruby Bridges on her first day at her new school in Louisiana?", "answer": "6 years old", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0cd", "question": "What Mexican revolutionary nearly started a war with the US when he invaded a town in New Mexico in 1916?", "answer": "Pancho Villa", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bdc5", "question": "What is the traditional herb in pesto sauce?", "answer": "Basil", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396f3", "question": "What was John Wayne\u2019s nickname?", "answer": "The Duke", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c452", "question": "What are there 270 of in the average human baby but only 206 in an adult?", "answer": "Bones", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b2c4", "question": "What US state is represented by the figures of Oliver Morton and Lew Wallace in the Capitol's Statuary Hall?", "answer": "Indiana", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ffa5691c73aa70ea0b70b2c", "question": "Which city is traditionally said to be built on seven hills?", "answer": "Rome", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ef7", "question": "Whose sensei is a rat named Master Splinter?", "answer": "The Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fede3b36ce05a3942286dd5", "question": "In what hotel does Ben rendezvous with Mrs. Robinson in \"The Graduate\"?", "answer": "The Taft", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a185", "question": "In the cartoon \"Wacky Races\", who drove the Convert-a-Car?", "answer": "Professor Pat Pending", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b195", "question": "Which battle brought the end of Napoleon's European conquests?", "answer": "Battle of Waterloo", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b7c3", "question": "Where was the first YouTube video filmed?", "answer": "In a zoo", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113398fb", "question": "What Madonna video won the 1998 MTV Video of the Year Award?", "answer": "Ray of Light", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c7ec", "question": "What is the astronomical term for three celestial bodies aligning?", "answer": "Syzygy", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b49", "question": "Where did the Pied Piper play?", "answer": "Hamelin", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fdab94a0b8cce1e6fda7054", "question": "Which person is known for publishing \"The Interpretation of Dreams\"?", "answer": "Sigmund Freud", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c75d", "question": "In the eye, what is the more common name for the condition also known as \"lens opacity\"?", "answer": "Cataract", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5feddc4a6ce05a3942286d9a", "question": "\"A Charlie Brown Christmas\" greatly influenced the sales of what product?", "answer": "Aluminum Christmas Trees", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5922002ba4edfd43a087add7", "question": "A \"Panatela\" is a type of what?", "answer": "Cigar", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe1ec44145fb29466707386", "question": "What vegetable's name in French translates to \"earth apple\"?", "answer": "Potato", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a84b", "question": "What \"colorful\" Sea lies between northeast China and the Korean peninsula?", "answer": "Yellow Sea", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fdfbedf003d27d341092bd2", "question": "Where is the world's largest tropical orchid garden?", "answer": "Singapore", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e60", "question": "Who provided the original voice for Stewie Griffin?", "answer": "Seth MacFarlane", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b50e", "question": "What was the date of the first day of the 21st century?", "answer": "January 1st, 2001", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd2d9772596a59cbdfbd3c5", "question": "Which Wild West crime was last documented on December 5, 1916?", "answer": "Stagecoach robbery", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a6da", "question": "The Bering Strait separates Russia from which US state?", "answer": "Alaska", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bdbb", "question": "What animal was used in British coal mines until being phased out in 1986?", "answer": "Canaries", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5f9f3f3eaf848b908361b86b", "question": "What amusement ride was first ridden in 1893 at the World's Columbian Exposition in Chicago?", "answer": "The Ferris Wheel", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b2f6", "question": "What union did Jimmy Hoffa head until his 1975 disappearance?", "answer": "The Teamsters", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133927d", "question": "In season 13 of the TV show \"Big Brother\" what is the name of the alliance that included Dominic, Cassie, Keith and Lawon?", "answer": "The Regulators", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe378ce0ada16518afdc054", "question": "Which popular Christmas song was originally written for a Broadway musical?", "answer": "\"White Christmas\"", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c99c", "question": "What is the more common name for the star cluster, Pleiades?", "answer": "Seven Sisters", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0d2", "question": "What guitar player was the last act to perform at the original Woodstock in 1969?", "answer": "Jimi Hendrix", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe4dda006d333868d34d705", "question": "Which Aegean Island's volcanic eruption may have possibly produced the Atlantis legend?", "answer": "Thera", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5af259acb63e5727cf5a4851", "question": "Which rock band released the singles \"Karma Police\" and \"Creep\"?", "answer": "Radiohead", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c8a7", "question": "Which element of the periodic table is named for a Scottish village?", "answer": "Strontium", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a6d8", "question": "Princeton University is located in which state?", "answer": "New Jersey", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ed1", "question": "What reality show gave America the catchphrase \"That's hot\"?", "answer": "The Simple Life", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c106", "question": "Where would you find a Walloon?", "answer": "Belgium", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b944", "question": "Whose 502-foot Fenway Park homer is marked by a single red seat in the right field bleachers?", "answer": "Ted Williams'", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba9b", "question": "What chapel do Cardinals congregate in to elect a new Pope?", "answer": "Sistine Chapel", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd96e8b23c87fd04dd15e39", "question": "What year was the current American flag designed?", "answer": "1958", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be07", "question": "Frank Sinatra was buried with a bottle of what whiskey?", "answer": "Jack Daniel's", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b919", "question": "What popular snack food was invented in Italy in 610 AD, and was shaped to look like a child's are folded in prayer?", "answer": "A pretzel", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf7f", "question": "How many lanes does an olympic standard swimming pool have?", "answer": "Eight", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fb088cccf631c2414a13b5c", "question": "Which house only became one of the Great Houses of Westeros after Aegon Targaryen\u2019s invasion?", "answer": "House Tyrell", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a4e5", "question": "The Caribbean island of Aruba is part of what European kingdom?", "answer": "The Netherlands", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd22", "question": "According to Pliny the Elder, what word do we get from the Roman practice of paying soldiers in salt?", "answer": "Salary", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5a1e1d47b5a031299b745739", "question": "During which century did Norsemen discover and settle in Greenland?", "answer": "10th Century", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b32d", "question": "Which Olympics did the US boycott?", "answer": "1980", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58d1164d4fea7fe947a2226e", "question": "What year was the film \"The Fly\", starring Jeff Goldblum, released in theaters?", "answer": "1986", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb69", "question": "What tennis player was named \"Sexiest Woman in the World\" by FHM magazine in 2002?", "answer": "Anna Kournikova", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a763", "question": "In which US state does the Rio Grande river begin?", "answer": "Colorado", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "58b0ea3b964118b2bb3809cf", "question": "What year did the \"ILOVEYOU\" virus began infecting computers worldwide?", "answer": "2000", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339491", "question": "What highway were Mickey and Mallory travelling in the movie \"Natural Born Killers\"?", "answer": "Highway 666", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59008ee5cf842fa4c4ba96b6", "question": "What were \"Jelly Babies\" renamed to in 1918 to mark the end of World War I?", "answer": "Peace Babies", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9d6", "question": "What large red flower is the floral emblem of New South Wales?", "answer": "Waratah", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6015f031fe83fe1f2a824c10", "question": "The total number of years the Israelites spent in captivity is?", "answer": "430 -- The Israelite spent about 430 years in Egypt.", "category": "history"}]